Am
we are we are we are
y'all. We are very lucky
and it is very fortuitous that you have
JOINED TODAY. OH WOW. NOW I'M ON THE
SHOW.
>> You made it. I I made it. We are joined
by I feel like astrologologist is just
too basic of a like there's got I feel
like there has to be there's like a word
before astrolog if you're not using that
I I need you to find because you're not
just an astrologologist. I've met
astrologologists.
You're like a
You're like a prophetess.
>> Ooh, the oracle.
>> Yeah, the loracle.
>> The
I knew I could count on um a Mercury and
Gemini person to give me the right
title.
>> The Laura.
>> Um are you able to turn your mic up at
all?
Um,
let me see my mic.
>> I feel like you're a little low and I'm
trying to turn it up on my end, but
>> Okay.
>> Is this better?
>> Yes. Yes.
>> Okay.
>> And you are giving us such Asian shimmer
shine flavor today. Like this is very
Asian rich Asian auntie. THIS IS VERY
I dressed up for you.
This is very that bad. So, for those who
don't know, Laura Chong, I don't know if
you know this, you know, you were on our
first episode of You Maneland.
>> I was.
>> Yes. You were my first You were You were
literally the first It was Roywood Jr.
and you.
>> Oh my gosh, I'm so honored.
>> So, I'm very happy to welcome you back.
It's been a year and some a couple ch a
couple like little weeks of change. And
when you came on, you gave us the
the horoscope, the reading, so to speak,
of the United States. And um but I know
that you look at things comprehensively.
So even when you're talking about the
US, you're talking about it within the
context of the world, which for the
record, a lot of people don't. They just
kind of think about the US as if it's in
its own silo. So, I'm going to leave the
floor to you.
>> Okay.
>> Take us on a journey.
>> Okay. Well, we could do it one of two
ways. We could do it more
conversationally or I did prepare
slides.
>> So, slides.
>> Okay. I see this uh present button. So,
um
>> you're able to access that.
>> Okay. Share screen.
Can I allow share screen?
Oops. There you are.
>> Okay. Wait.
>> Oh, wait.
>> Oh. Oh my gosh. I think I clicked the
wrong thing. Um,
>> I think you go present and then you go
slides
at the top.
>> Slides. Okay.
>> Oh, your computer.
>> Yep.
>> Oh, but they're on my computer. So, I
just want to share the screen. Okay.
>> Okay. So, you can share the screen.
>> Okay.
Can I do this? Yep. And then make it
full screen.
>> Can you see this? I can. Yes.
Okay.
But make it
the viewer.
There we go. This
Okay.
>> This picture. I know this gif so well.
Okay. The only thing is I can't see your
face or anything. I just see my screen.
>> Oh, okay. We can see you. Okay.
>> Okay. Good. Um, and I can't see my
notes. So, I'm going to try my best to
do this off of memorization.
>> You have it in your phone.
>> Um, I do.
>> There we go.
>> Okay. Look at you being so um
>> Yeah. And my brain is so full. So, if I
have to look at my notes, I might have
to do that. Okay.
>> Why is your brain so full? I mean, I I
know why.
>> Oh my god. Cuz there's so many dates and
like things that I think I want to
share, but I know we have How much time
do we have? Like 30 minutes,
>> however long you want.
>> Okay. Um, but at the end of this, I want
to give people something helpful like
how to use this astrology because I
don't want to just like trauma dump on
you and be like, "This is all happening
and goodbye." Um
because
because ultimately it's us preparing
ourselves for what's coming. It's like
ast a astrological weather. Just as if
you were listening to the weather report
and the weatherman says it's going to
rain or it's going to snow. You want to
like dress appropriately. You want to be
prepared for something.
>> Yep. So, and when I've done these
things, when I've done these reports for
other, you know, podcasts and stuff, I
always lead with I don't mean to
fear-monger, but I think a little fear
is helpful now at this point in 2026.
Not
>> for you to be in your trigger response,
but for you to do something.
>> Yes.
>> 2026 is the year to act. Yeah.
>> And I think when I came on last year, I
said this is the preparatory year. 2025
is like the glimpse, the preview. And
now we're in it. And I mean, we all see
we are in it. Two weeks into 2026.
>> In it.
>> We're in it. Okay. So, I'm going to
basically show the major astrological
transits. I'm not going to show all of
them, but some of them. and then um how
it relates to us as a collective. And if
you want to know how this impacts you at
an individual level, I am teaching
astrology 101 again. Amanda took my
class. I feel like I should take it
again.
>> Oh, well, we start next Wednesday. So,
if anybody's interested, you can follow
up and um and learn from me how to read
your needle chart. Uh, so I think I've
gone through all the disclaimers. So,
are we ready?
You're like, okay, so the first major
transit is January 26, which is this
month. Um, Neptune will enter the sign
of Aries.
And we experienced this transit last
summer between May and between March and
November. And Neptune is the planet that
is about our imagination, our dreams.
It's it is like the illusion. And um I
did a whole episode of Neptune on my
podcast with a fellow astrologer,
Camille Michelle Gray, and how we
believe the United States uses Neptune
and this illusion of white supremacy to
sort of like put us in a haze, in a fog.
And depending on your journey with your
white adjacency or your internalized
white supremacy is how you start to
awaken from that dream, American dream,
quote unquote.
So, a lot of astrologers relate Neptune
and Aries.
Nept I could only hear your sound, your
like sound effects cuz I can't cuz I
can't see you. Um because I'm just like
But I want you to turn your mic up a
little more because you're saying all
the things.
>> Okay.
Um
let me see if I could do that from here.
>> Um
I'm not sure I can do that when I'm in
the presentation. Can you hear me? Let
me just be closer to the mic.
>> Okay. Can you hear me?
>> Yes.
>> Is this better?
Yes,
>> that's better.
>> I just feel like you're saying such
important things like I don't want it to
be lost.
>> Okay.
>> How do you feel in the chat?
>> Do y'all feel like you can hear her fine
and everything? Cuz it could be just me.
All right. They've all said that they
can hear you fine. So, let me just shit
it up.
Oh,
okay. So, back to Can you hear me?
>> Yes. And I also want to shout out
Rolando because you just got them before
I could.
>> Are people not behaving? Are people
>> No, they're not. People are in here
like, Amanda, you're but you're beyond
reproach and it's hard to consume your
content. So then don't
o
>> don't don't consume it. I am above
reproach by strangers on the internet
behind fake names and fake faces.
Correct. I am above your rep. I am
reproach. What is it? Unrapproachable.
Yeah. You want to see me in the street
and have a conversation per se? Then we
can do that. But no, I am I am above the
reproach of strangers on the internet.
That is correct. Very astute. Kudos to
them. They are not hiding behind a he
they are not in a cloud of Neptune. They
see the truth.
Oh my goodness.
>> I love what you said about
so Neptune is a m like but I love what
you said about like the wielding
of the dreaminess of Neptune but for an
for a a a um duplicitous purpose because
I feel like I would never you know what
I mean like I would never consider that
but then we have to remember there's
like shadow and light to everything.
>> Yes. And Neptune is it it also
symbolizes like the film industry
because when Neptune entered Aries
around the Civil War is when film
photography was invented. So, I also
like as a positive transit, what I liked
about Neptune and Aries last summer, we
got sinners and we got K-pop demon
hunters and there were films created by
the global majority in and like original
content, you know, from the POV of
people of the global majority. And so, I
did like that aspect of that transit.
And hopefully when Neptune enters Aries
for the next 14 years, we get more
like original art from people of the
global majority in terms of film and art
and music.
>> Mhm. Yep.
>> Yep. So a lot of astrologers,
you know, they relate this transit to
the civil war because that was the last
time Neptune entered Aries. And um so we
are already in a civil war. Um I hope
everyone is on board with that.
>> Wait, say that again.
>> We are already in a civil war right now.
>> You're right. Yeah, we are
>> because of I mean it looks like
Minneapolis is sort of the epicenter or
it's the start of it, but uh we saw this
last summer too. That was also the rise
of ICE and and I think it was Los
Angeles and Chicago we saw that and um
yeah so yeah yeah it's happening and you
know at the time when these wars started
the civil war and uh you know they
didn't they didn't say we are in war it
just sort of like happened you know
>> we are in war
>> it It wasn't until like in hindsight
these specific events were the catalyst
for these moments.
>> Um Fatima here said, you know, I don't
know what to call this area. It's beyond
this era. It's beyond a civil war. I
think what it what I think for what it's
worth, when we're in times that are new
times, we use language that we've
>> used. Yeah. And then it isn't until we
can reflect that we're like, you know
what,
that might we we may need something new
for that.
>> Yeah. And and yeah, I think our
definition of war is limited to what
we've experienced previously.
>> Yes.
>> Because I don't think what's happening
in Gaza or Sudan are wars.
>> But they use that word.
>> Yeah. So,
>> because anything that's just like the
height of violence, they're like war and
that's just too generic.
>> Exactly.
And for those of you who don't know, the
Civil War was between the South and the
North and they basically the South
basically fought to keep slavery. Um, I
know I'm like just glazing over a lot of
the
but that was the crux. So, um, this war
quote unquote that we're in is ICE,
which are
it just seems like it's Trump's or like
these this administration's
private army, right? Would you consider
this to be a militia type of thing?
Maybe. Um,
>> yeah,
>> that's the goal.
>> Yes. And
also during the Neptune and Aries era
was um the Emancipation Proclamation.
And I I I can't say the word that you
use for this, but it's basically in my
opinion a performative
sort of
proclamation to free slaves. Um, but it
wasn't Abraham Lincoln didn't actually
free the slaves. It was more just a law
that was performative, but they he they
like the this government didn't do
anything in forms of reparations or
integrating them into the system.
No. Oh, and I mean he
barely passed
um the 13th amendment and then he was
assassinated two weeks after the civil
war and any efforts that had been put
forth like special field order 51 which
was the 40 acres in a mule and for the
record that wasn't for everybody that
was just like in a small port part of
the south even that got re retracted and
they took the land back from folks and
then they put in the black laws. So,
>> you know, he he I will say this, Abraham
Lincoln was forced by black leaders to
understand the value of black people
to his goal. And he saw that it was more
valuable to have them free than
enslaved. But any I feel like any I mean
he does a speech where he's like, you
know, y'all see them with guns and now
you now you rock with them now because
you see them with guns.
And he that's essentially what he says.
And then he's like, you know, um I you
know, y'all y'all need to represent
because black people, they deserve a
right to to pop off, too. But as we
know, all of these presidents are just
basically actors, so they'll say what
needs to get said.
>> Yeah. Yes.
And
Yes. So, um, also, if anybody has
questions, you can pop them in the chat
and Amanda can read them to me, but
maybe that's for the end.
>> Um, and then February 13th, Saturn will
enter Aries. And again we experienced
this transit last year uh during between
like May and November. And Saturn is the
planet of boundaries, borders,
the authority hierarchy. And it is a
malefific planet. So it does bring
challenges. But we need Saturn because
Saturn in Greek mythology is Kronos.
It's time. It's also a timekeeper in
astrology. But Saturn is what's called
in its fall in Aries. So Saturn as a
planet is about patience and discipline
and you know doing something for the
long term whereas Aries as an archetype
is like let's do it now you know and
Aries is the archetype of
>> you are an Aries right
>> I am an Aries yes
>> which is why but which is why I push
people cuz I just don't think this is a
time to be complacent or just like
sitting back and waiting for people you
Now, Aries is about listening to your
like reclaiming your inner authority
instead of waiting for somebody to tell
you what to do or like get or waiting
for somebody to give you the answers.
It's like you have to have that self
initiative to be like, you know, cuz I
hear people asking me all the time, what
should I be doing? What, you know, and
I'm just like,
>> and maybe it's cuz I'm a I was a latch
key kid. Like, we just I just figured
out how to cook. I just figured out how
to do things, you know.
>> Yes.
>> No, that's so it's so real. I mean, my
friend um who who does my newsletter,
she was telling me yesterday that she
told her daughter that they are now
living in the '9s and thus she has
implemented some ways in which her
daughter has to live in the 90s. So like
she can't binge TV shows. She has to
watch one show one night a week and like
you know what I mean? like she and she's
what she's doing is she's quelling her
um
her instinct to get instant
gratification which is what I think also
leads to people being like tell me what
to do because it's like you can just
type into Google and it will tell you
what to do and it's like people then try
and Google people they treat people like
they are a search engine tell me what to
do
>> yes
>> you know and I'm like and uh I I donate
to a nonprofit in in um Kenya that pays
for school for Kenyon children. And she
was telling me that a lot of the
curriculum is not to
encourage thought, it's to encourage
like a willingness to be led. Um, and so
she was like, you know, when she would
teach classes, like sometimes they would
look at her crazy when she'd be like,
"What do you think?" And they'd be like,
"Lady, what's the answer?
>> What? Tell us." And so I feel like
that's we like we how I feel like in my
epiphany of like wanting to do more with
this show, I feel like what you're
saying is what I'm trying to do, which
is like how do I bring the Aries out of
people more?
>> Let's be more into people's Aries. And
we're about to go into 20 years of fire.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. Well, well, people are going to be
forced to because the energy this year
is a lot of fire and air and it's going
to be the year of the young fire horse,
which there's just going to be a lot of
momentum and yeah, I think it's going to
be an uncomfortable year for people if
you are uncomfortable with change.
>> So, um, okay. So on February 17th, we
have our first solar eclipse in the Leo
Aquarius axis and a solar eclipse is a
new moon and this is at 28°. So just
remember that degree and put a pin on it
for a moment. Um February 20th is sort
of the biggest transit that astrologers
have been looking out for. Saturn and
Neptune will come together in a
conjunction at 0 degrees of Aries. and 0
degrees in the cardinal signs is a world
point. So that is a really big deal. And
then on March 3rd, there will be a lunar
eclipse at 12° of Virgo. So I just want
to go ahead a little bit and show all of
you the can you see this the chart of so
the inner ring is the United States
natal chart. I mean there's many natal
charts but most astrologers use the
sibly chart and it's about the time when
the declaration of independence was
signed and then on the outer re wheel is
the emancipation proclamation on January
1st 1863
and so as you can see by the circles the
the the outer so the outer ring is when
the Emancipation Proclamation
>> I see what you're saying so we're
comparing the two
>> yes cuz that's like by transit, right?
>> Yeah.
>> So, you can see where I circled in this
bottom half um the United States IC or
imum coali, which is the roots of a
chart. It's essentially like what like
the most private section of someone's
like natal chart is. And the United
States has an IC of one degrees of
Aries. And so
>> at the time of the emancipation
proclamation, Neptune was conjunct the
United States IC. Exactly.
>> So some something about like people's
dreams and freedom was changing at that
time, right? That was when this um you
know emancipation proclamation and then
the opposite was Saturn in Libra where
Saturn has this exaltation conjunct the
United States midheaven and the
midheaven in someone's chart is about
their public persona what they're known
for and the United States has a Libra
midheaven which is like the United
States is known for supposedly fairness
and justice for all right M
>> so that Saturn Neptune opposition was
the emancipation proclamation and now
February of February 20th 2026 Saturn
will be in Aries with Neptune on the
United States I see.
So now we're like completing that
opposition that cycle from that moment
if that makes sense. What's the
significance of completing the cycle?
>> Something about the United States
Foundation is changing again.
>> Okay.
>> And it's rhyming with that emancipation
proclamation chart time with Saturn and
Neptune. And like I mentioned when I was
speaking about Saturn and Aries.
>> Okay, I get it. I get it. I get it.
>> Just so y'all know, like I I have a
delayed reaction to everything Laura
says about astrology. I have to run it a
good six times through the processor and
THEN I'M LIKE, "OH,
>> YES." BUT WHEN you get it, I'm like,
"Yes,
we did it, Joe.
>> We did it.
We did it, Joe. We did it, Joe."
Um, but like I said, the emancipation
proclamation with Saturn in its
exaltation in in Libra was sort of like,
okay, we're just going to give them this
law. Gosh. You know, and you have a you
have
>> you know what I call that? I know you're
not allowed to say it, but I call it the
hair nigga damn law.
>> Yes. But I couldn't say it.
>> OH, THAT'S WHAT YOU WERE SAYING EARLIER
that you couldn't say
>> I was like I
>> I was like, what is she saying that she
can't say? Yes. These are the here nigga
damn laws where they're just like here
nigga damn.
>> Yes.
>> Cuz cuz Libra is about fairness but it
can often times be like neutral or
performative, right? And Saturn again is
like
>> Yes. And so
>> trying to be liked by everyone.
>> Yes.
>> Okay.
>> But you have to remember what the
context is here. We're talking about the
United States of America. And so they're
only out for their own interest. Like
the United States system is working how
it's designed essentially.
>> It's working exactly how it was designed
um for them, but not for anybody who's
not a white man.
Well, I think the thing we also have to
remember is that the United States was
designed to carry out the greater goal
of Zionist supremacy which centers white
men
>> whiteness. Yeah.
>> And you know the same way that Britain
was a tool as well and that's why
Britain and the United States were both
used effectively to create Israel
>> um as like a home as a home base for
Zionism. And so like when we see the
creation of the United States, we are
told the Neptunian lie that it was
created in the goal of reol of like
revolution of freedom of um you know
self-identification
when it was really created in the for in
the pursuit of expansion
>> of the very same folks that they were
mad at or that they claimed they were
mad at. Like they were basically like,
"We don't want to be taxed by your
banks, so we're going to start our own."
>> Yes.
>> Slave owners owning slave. I mean, it's
slaves becoming slave owners.
>> Yes. And every empire needs a myth and a
lore that people believe in.
>> And the thing the thing with Neptune is
>> it's real and you believe in something
that's reality until you don't. And so
that's why in the last couple of years
the United States was going through its
Neptune opposition because the United
States has Neptune in Virgo and for the
last 14 years Neptune has been in
Pisces. People have been waking up.
>> Yes.
>> Waking up to the fact that oh the
American dream is actually not a dream.
You have to put in the labor. You have
to put in the work. You have to be of
service to the empire. So
>> that's why people have been waking up in
the last 14 years and that work as like
somehow
>> um like moral or like that's like that
that you serving empire is you doing the
right thing, right? Like that's how it's
been presented.
>> Yes. Yes.
Because one aspect of like a shadow
aspect of Virgo is being of service and
not necessarily sometimes for the better
like the for the good of all you know.
Uh so now with Saturn in Aries, Saturn
is in its fall and again my colleague
and I were sort of commiserating on this
and saying this is actually good for us
like the people because we need Saturn
in its fall to collapse structures and
because again Aries is not a
performative
sign. It's like I'm doing this because
this is the best for like myself. Um
hopefully we we get out of the
individualistic mindset of the United
States. But like Saturn and Neptune
coming together on the United States IC
is for us a good thing. I believe
>> Saturn and Neptune coming together on
the United States IC is a good thing
because it destroys structures. It
destroys the foundation. It destroy it
dissolves the the foundation of the
United States and we get to shape what
that looks like. But I don't I don't
think we're ever going to get ahead
until we as a people, specifically white
Americans, grapple with what their
ancestors did to the indigenous people
of Turtle Island and reparations. Like
those two things.
>> It's so true because Saturn is also like
you reap what you seow. It is the It is
the god of the land. It's the scythe.
It's Yes. Remember it's the scythe. And
Saturn is the god of the agriculture of
the land. And who
>> literally tilled the land of the United
States, built all the wealth of the
United States. like that has to be sewed
in some way, you know? So unless we as a
people of the United States,
specifically white Americans, again, I'm
going to repeat it, we grapple with that
and we all come together and say this
portion of the money that the United
States has goes to the descendants of,
you know, the child slavery and
reparations for the indigenous people,
Turtle Island. Like, I don't know how we
can go forward to be honest.
>> Well, it's a karma correction, right? It
is. I mean, it's also that like it's
like it's an actual like
>> karma correction. I'm sure it's it's
very science, you know, to every action
there's equal and opposite reaction.
Like it's a it's a
>> a level setter. It's a
>> it's a law of physics.
>> It's a law of physics. It's a it's a
it's a it's a you know what it is? It's
a controlled burn.
>> That's what it is. like and they have to
see that the burning of their forest
>> is for the greater good of the whole
forest. And they
>> and you know the problem with that
though to me Laura is that
>> it's like it can't be forced upon. It's
like when you try and date somebody and
like you want them to change but it's
like they if they don't want to change
nothing can be done. So then it becomes
like
>> it can't be forced upon. And then I'm
like, well, so
>> if it can't be forced upon, then we're
really just expecting all these white
people to wake up. Which is why I'm
constantly like
>> white people who are woken up, you have
to be like it has to be like your
literal
>> like purpose to wake up the white people
around you like sitting like sitting
eating your Cheerios like, okay, what
tactic are we going to deploy today?
Mhm.
There was this thread on on threads that
this like white woman was like, "I'm
calling upon Kalima and Yameya." And I'm
like, "Girl, stop calling on these
goddesses. Talk to your white brothers,
white fathers, white sons." I'm like,
"We don't need you to call upon. Leave
them alone. Like, they're not even a
part of your like pantheon of cosmos."
So I'm just like talk to your
problematic fathers, brothers. Like
that's your role.
>> Not you. Not you hanging up the phone.
>> Oh my god. I am I am such a
>> She said, "What would the ancestors
say?" You said, "Boo." No. No. Click
click. No.
>> Um I'd be I'd be all up in the in those
threads. But that's why I speak to
people it through the lens of
spirituality and trying to explain to
people that there is a there is like a
an acrruel of a cruel why can't I
pronounce that word? Uh maybe it's my
Asianness coming out. Um a cruel of
karmic debt.
>> Okay.
>> White people like have epigenetically
inherited something. Um, and so in order
for you to clear your bloodlines and be
the good ancestor, you have to be part
of the solution.
>> This it's the same way that like so many
of us who are oppressed have
intergenerational DNA, right? Inter
intergenerational trauma. There is no
reason why white people would also not
have the same effects.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. deal with it.
>> I watched I know you know I know you
know Christina Brown, but I watched her
video recently of like white people's
epigenetics and
>> I I was just like, "Okay, white people
used to eat black people." What?
>> And you and then you're walking around
saying
>> and like used black people as like
furniture, whatever. And then you're
walking around saying, "I'm too scared."
like your your ancestors colonized
because they thought they were entitled
to.
>> Yeah. It's the same way like I watched a
video the other day of this woman in
Zimbabwe and she was they were asking
her about you know who does she have any
like servants and she's like yes you
know I have servants you know and I I'm
I'm very happy with the life we have we
have made here in Zimbabwe. Um but the
it is in 1979 and she was like you know
but I don't see why we would give the
just hand it back over to the to hand it
over to the Africans. I mean after we
have worked so hard to build our lives
here and everyone in the comments was
like stealing is not hard work like
stop calling stealing we worked hard
like that's an unfair disingenuous
positioning of what you have done.
That's how Americans look at it. Like we
built this country up. No,
>> you broke people down.
>> They also were just dirty. They brought
diseases. Sorry, I know we're going off
tangent, but like expected.
Um, so that okay, so that is the Saturn
and Neptune conjunction and it's
happening a month from now. So again
like these transits
are longer cycles but the exact is
happening on February 20th.
Oh
yes fe February 20th. Um so remember
back when I said put a pin on the solar
eclipse.
>> Yeah. So the solar eclipse which also is
the lunar new year uh because the lunar
new year happens on the new moon in
Aquarius every year. Um is that also
Ramadan? Is that also I think Ramadan is
they
>> maybe this year
>> they I think it's the new moon. Um
so this solar eclipse is happening
exactly on the United States natal moon
>> and the moon in a nation's chart
represents the people
>> so us.
Uh so I do think that hopefully this
portends to an awakening of some kind
for us to like really organize. Um
because there's a difference between
activism and organizing and I think we
need organizing. Didn't Malcolm X say
that we're not outnumbered? We're just
not
>> we're out organized.
>> Yeah. Exactly.
>> Yeah. So, that is the solar eclipse and
um
Oh, okay. So, how are we doing on time?
Should I keep going or
>> We're here.
>> This is the first show of the year. I
have things to share, but ultimately
we're here and I knew that um I didn't
have a second guest today because I knew
that this was going to be thorough.
>> Okay. Okay. Uh just let me know when
you're like, "Okay, this is too much."
Um
>> well, that's the chat. I mean, because
you know, I'll sit here and do this with
you all day, but considering that the we
have a high number of viewers and the
chat is in the mix, I'm sure everyone is
fine.
>> Okay, great.
>> You're very good at your job.
>> Even though you're not employed.
>> On April 25th, Uranus will enter the
sign of Gemini. And we also experienced
this a last year. So again, 2025 was
like the preview of what were kind of
these longer cycles and both Neptune,
Uranus and Uranus and including Pluto
these are outer planets. So this is
these are like the generational planets.
So um Uranus and Gemini every so the
United States has Uranus and Gemini in
its chart. So it always like portends to
war and also technological advances.
Uh so um yeah, that's going to happen
April 25th on June 9th. I really wanted
to add like a juicy nice little transit
for everybody to look out for. Venus
>> with this little mouth with
>> Yeah.
>> It's like sexy time juicy day. Okay.
>> Okay. Um because honestly we need to
like dance and make out again, you know,
because so many leftists are so
depressed and
I really miss making out. I'm so good at
it and I just I like doing things I'm
good at. Like I really like I'm telling
you like I don't even need to have sex.
I just want a good
>> make out sesh.
>> Yeah. Like a makeout can will carry me
over for another two years. a solid make
out session. And I mean even like we can
just be like above the clothes. We could
just be second basing and I would be
>> fine.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean I remember I still
like remember the nightclub days where
you would just like be dancing till 2
a.m. and making out with a stranger. I
don't know if people do that anymore
because of like
>> the times are and the times are
different but
>> u I did that in Cuba. It was a time
>> it was a time. Can I just tell a quick
sidebar story that I went in I walked
into the club in Cuba
>> and I spotted an individual and I turned
to my home girl Kiki and I was like that
one and she was like okay.
And so we went about our lives and we
were in the club for a good hour and a
half and then he came up to me.
>> Oo. So you manifested.
>> I manifested it. The club had like all
these different rooms. So, it wasn't
like we were just like in the same
space. I freaking manifested it. I was
literally standing at the bar and then I
turned to my right and he was right
there and I was like, "Hello,
>> hello."
And man, that was a good solid. We made
out on the Malikon on the wall.
>> Oo. By the water.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, that's a Venus and Jupiter in in
Cancer sort of moment.
It was a time. I'll pull up a picture
for you all. But good.
>> They like these types of things. It
reminds them that, you know, I've lived
a life. I've lived a life, Laura. I've
lived a life.
>> Yes. Oh, man.
>> Right. Oh, man.
>> Um, well, I'm just thinking of life pre,
you know,
Yeah. all of like awakening, you know,
cuz with awakening you can't go back cuz
you can't not see what you see. So
>> with awakening you can't go back.
You can't not see what you see. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> Cuz now you have a different
>> you have a different framework of seeing
everything, you know?
I mean, you also just like
you either you're either choosing
willful ignorance or you know what I
mean because that that's your only
option.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> So, we are here at Arte,
>> my husband, my Cuban husband,
he's going to come to America and find
me.
Amanda,
he's fine.
So, we are here at
Gong Ray,
>> my husband,
>> my husband, my Cuban husband.
He's going to come to America and find
me. Yeah,
>> I've lived a life.
Look at Laura's face, y'all.
>> Wait, I I didn't realize he was also
really good-looking.
>> That was the requisite.
I guess that was literally the only
thing it was based on.
>> Wow.
I wasn't like making out with his
character. It was like, okay, you
>> I wasn't making out with this character.
Oh my god.
Whoa. Wait. I love that this brought us
to this side tangent cuz that's like a
good visual of what you can manifest for
this transit, y'all.
>> There you go.
>> It's possible.
>> It's possible. Cuz
I really feel like Laura, like these
people don't really understand that I
was that girl. Like because I really be
in here with my glasses and my sweaters
and they don't understand. I was I was a
hot girl. I was out here.
>> Why would Wait, why wouldn't they think
that?
>> I don't know. They don't. They don't.
They think I'm an auntie. They think
that I'm just, you know, wearing my
glasses and teaching. You know, they
don't understand. I was in the world.
>> Listen,
we're multifaceted women. Okay.
>> We are. Y'all have never seen Laura
whine to some reggae. Okay.
>> I was going to say when people see me
out in the wild, they're like, "Wow,
you're fun."
>> It was so irritating to me when people
were like, "I would never invite Amanda
to a party. She's too serious." I'm
like, "What?"
>> That's what I'm saying. Like we leftists
or what I don't know what what we even
call ourselves. Radical revolutionaries.
Like that's why I'm saying we have to
shake our ass. We have to have fun.
because these people are depressed and
then they start to project their own
trauma onto people in the movement
lateral violence.
>> So the I think healing healing work and
doing the internal work is part of this
liberation movement. Yeah,
>> absolutely. And it's a necessary part
when you're
you're literally
your opponents when when they say like
the um the cruelty cruelty is the goal.
Like that's not just a catchphrase.
That's literally what feeds these
people. So like the same thing that you
get like we may get serotonin relief and
you know endorphine relief from I mean
release from seeing you know cute
animals or from dancing or from being
around our friends and laughing. They in
some twisted way they get it from seeing
pain. Why am I echo e echoing?
I don't know why. Um but they get it
from seeing the misery of others.
>> Mhm.
>> You know what I mean? And so that's an
actual tool against them is not letting
them make you miserable.
>> Yeah.
>> I wanted to try this. Um, I downloaded
the slides if that's okay.
>> Yeah, because if you bring them up as a
PDF, you'll be able to see yourself and
see me on the thing.
>> Okay, great.
I'm waiting for you.
>> Oh, it's processing.
>> Okay. No, I was just I just wanted you
to know like I'm not like the floor is
yours. Um,
>> I just uploaded them. Okay.
Not that Ekko is giving Galadriel.
I could be the most powerful.
Okay, they're uploaded, but how come I
can't see them? Oh, there they are.
Okay. Yes, this is so much better.
Um, okay. So, Venus and Jupiter are the
bonificics in astrology. So when they
come together in the sky, this is such a
great day to manifest somebody to make
out with, to grow something. Venus is
the planet of our relationships, values,
what we like want to invest in. Jupiter
is the planet of expansion, knowledge,
growth. Um, and Jupiter is in its
exaltation in cancer. So, this is a day
I like had to highlight it to like
launch something, do something that just
is like um I mean Amanda said she made
out with someone by the water. It's like
cancer is a water sign. Cancer is also
about nurturing and mothering and and
protection. So, yeah, this is just a
great day. And then June 30th, Jupiter
will enter the sign of Leo. Again, we're
having all of these planets sort of move
to fire and air signs. And fire and air
are complimementaryary elements cuz you
need
>> they're dry.
>> Yes, they're dry. They You need air to
grow fire. Um,
>> right. I'm just trying to think of my my
my uh
>> your notes. Yes,
>> my flash cards.
Um, and then on July 4th, this is
definitely a day to maybe be careful.
Um, because not only is it the 250th
birthday of the United States, it
there's a Mars and Uranus conjunction in
Gemini at 3°. And Mars is um the god of
war. In Babylonian astrology, it was the
god of death before Pluto came along. It
is conflict, anger, action, and Uranus
is the planet of revolution and change
and revelation. So,
>> what is the planet you said that was of
like technology and stuff?
>> Uranus.
>> Okay. That's what I thought.
>> Yeah. So,
>> damn.
>> Yeah. I I personally wouldn't.
>> It's very B for vendetta.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I wouldn't go to me
personally. I wouldn't just from where
it is in my chart. Like I wouldn't go
out to a public gathering per se. Um,
but everybody use your own intuition and
free will, but I definitely think
something is going to pop off in the
United States, so to speak.
Um, that's why you have the pew pew.
>> Yes, that's why I have the pew pew. Um
so even asked death by technology and
what I get from this combo Laura is the
like true implementation or like the
like a real
life
demonstration of
all the palunteer stuff that we've been
hearing about and you know all of the
surveillance stuff we've been hearing
about like coming to a head in like a
very real non like unable to be ignored
kind of way.
>> And
I just saw that basically Tony Blair and
um Oracle
they are building a competitor to
Palunteer. So now there's gonna be
because basically Larry Ellison is a
partner with Palunteer
>> and so because of his partnership with
Palunteer because he tried to buy
Palunteer and Palanteer was like
absolutely not but then they let him
partner with him and so he has access
because his a his AI modules have done
all the work for Palent like have have
done all the AI work. So he has like all
of the I I saw a video about this. So he
has all of the like um basically the
learning. He has all the knowledge of
the building of the systems
>> and now he's partnered with Tony Blair
>> and so he's just giving it all to Tony
Blair.
>> Oh,
>> but there's no honor amongst thieves.
You know what I mean? So it's like,
yeah, of course that would happen.
>> That's of course. Yeah.
Yes. But on the other hand, this could
be the United States, the people of the
United States fighting back in some way,
you know,
wink wink. Cuz I've already been seeing
I've already been seeing
I guess like the the what's it called?
Um the he's not he's not a leader of the
Black Panther Party, but he's becoming
more present on social media. Have you
seen
>> I literally have a video? Yeah, I think
you're talking about this person
right here. Hold on.
>> He's like walking around with a gigantic
>> Oh, no. That's a different brother
actually. But I know exactly
>> that.
>> He definitely he definitely was like
second amendment rights. I have my gun.
>> Yes. And he had he knew all the because
the Black Panther Party knew all the
laws, right? and he literally was like
section something something of the law
code and he had this gigantic um gun and
he basically was like to the cops y'all
are you know um
like get out of here you you we don't
know what you're even bitches get out of
here talking to two cops in Philly and
he was like
>> he was like y'all are coons why are you
here look
>> I can't say those words
>> I feel like you can say coon
>> no I don't want
Okay. Well, I'll say it for you. Y'all
are coons. And he was like, "There's no
reason for you to be here. Get out of
here." And they were like, "You have a
nice day." He said, "You have a terrible
day. You You have a terrible day."
>> Yes. Oh, such a good video. And that to
me is Mars and Uranus.
It's like the way that he was also just
so quick with his words and he was just
like boom boom boom. And how he was just
standing there with that gun. I was
like, "Wow, that man has presence."
That's Mars Uranus. It's also protecting
the neighborhood, right? Cuz Uranus is
Uranus and Gemini is about protecting
your own like smaller community. And um
yeah, that's like the best way to use
this energy.
>> Oh, I found it.
>> If Yeah,
>> I have it. Um
I love when I'm able to just pull up
what you were
>> I know. I love Wait, I love this. I love
that you have all these like amazing
clips to support my
presentation.
>> It's it's it's it's just a real um
Scotty Pippen Jordan. It was you don't
like to be labeled in with you shouldn't
have touching their whole sellout.
>> You are a sellout. You wearing their
shit. You are a sellout. You ain't
protecting shit. You got to do whatever
they tell you to, including hurt your
people.
>> Because you walking up to me and I don't
like you and I don't trust you and I
don't got no conversation with you. So
unless you investigating the crime,
leave me the fuck alone. No, when I'm
getting 911,
>> I don't care. I got a gun license right
here. This is legal. Philadelphia crime
code 6108. Move your car out of people's
way and get the fuck out of my face.
Thank you, officer.
>> Have a good day.
>> You have a bad one. Sell up. Fuck out of
here. You smiling for sellout. You know
where you came from? Slave catchers
hired you to help catch their property,
which was us. Slave catcher controls the
origin of our click ass. The fuck out of
here.
Go where you're needed. We don't need
your help. Get off the fucking street.
Get off the fucking street.
>> Let me just say something for those who
don't know cuz I I do understand that
there is a limitation of language, you
know, just out of respect for people.
And I do pity that y'all are not able to
use bitch ass nigga because it is I
don't know that there's any other, you
know, how they'll be like there's no
comparable word in the English language
for this. Like
>> I don't know that there's any other
comparable word for bitch ass nigga.
Like it's a very specific classification
of individual. And I have not I I
there's nothing there's no substitute
for it. So you know like I remember like
some of the worst arguments me and my
man ever got into was when I would be
what I when I would devolve into you
JUST BEING A BITCH ASS NIGGA. That is
worse than like I could say something
about anything else, but that right
there was like
>> if I was that cop, I would have been
crying.
>> He probably DID CRY IN THE CAR. He was
probably in the shower in the cop locker
room. Like
like that video gave me I watched it
like 20 times. It gave me so much
energy. I was like, "Oh my gosh." Mhm.
>> Cuz it was also just so unwavering
>> like get out of here. Get
>> it was very black Air Force One's black
Tims energy and I sure as heck did make
sure and they did wear a black twin Tims
which made perfect sense. Like it's a
very particular type of energy. Also
what y'all don't understand is that
Philly cats are really cut different.
You know like sometimes I think people
just think like it's the United States.
No. Like there's different different
energies come from different places.
Black men in Philly is a whole
particular sector. I mean WB Boys wrote
like a whole book on it. Like I'm just
like it's different.
>> I think Philly people are different.
They're like on a whole different level.
>> Well, you also remember how old
Philadelphia is.
>> True. It's OG OG colony state. Yeah.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> Yeah.
>> So, here we are. We're just tangenti.
This actually is actually really helpful
because it's letting me bring in like
other content.
>> Mhm.
>> You know, to to balance, not balance,
but to like even expound upon expound
>> expound
to expound
upon
what you're talking about. No, I love it
because it makes it less like like I'm
lecturing, but this is like a
conversation, you know?
>> It's a happy medium. Happy medium.
>> Happy medium.
>> Um and then there's like Black Panthers
just returning, you know, like Black
Panthers are definitely starting to
resurface. There's um another brother
I'm going to show y'all a little later
on. Or actually, I mean, can I just show
him now since we're on the topic of
Black Panthers?
Um,
>> this brother right here is, you know,
because a lot of folks really only know
about the Panthers in like a very kind
of pop culture context. And I talk about
the Panthers at length in what would the
ancestors say, giving more of a
>> of an overview of the Panthers as an
actual movement that for what for what
people don't understand is that they
were a movement that was effective.
That's what folks don't really
understand. And that is why they have
been, you know, rendered
um like terrorists and put to the
fringe. It's because they were
effective.
>> Mhm.
>> All power to the people. Chairman Paul
Beron reporting for ethic community
defense duty. Listen, two things that I
need to run by you. Thing number one is
um
a lot of people are saying that we
should not stand up against ICE because
we're standing up against we're standing
for people that aren't us. And uh Black
Panthers only stand for black people.
That is a lie. Huey P. Newton said that
we are internationalists and we stand
with all oppressed people no matter what
color they are.
That's the founder of the Black Panther
Party that said that. So everybody who's
running around talking about Black
Panthers don't stand up for people other
than black people don't know a damn
thing about the Black Panther Party.
That's thing number one. Thing number
two, the Black Panther Party created
something called the Rainbow Coalition,
which is a coalition of Hispanics,
Asians, whites, and blacks from all over
the world working together to fight
oppression. Again, the Black Panther
stood with the Mexicans, stood with the
uh Puerto Ricans and the Dominicans,
stood with the Japanese, the Vietnamese.
We actually, the Black Panthers did a
whole campaign to end the Vietnam War
because they they stood with Vietnam.
So for you guys who are talking all of
this gibberish about, oh, you're not you
guys aren't following traditions of the
original, who do you think that we're
who do you think our leaders are? Aaron
Dixon is an original Black Panther,
right?
>> Aaron Dixon is an original Black Panther
who walked with Hilly Newton. That
that's that's that's who we that's
that's our leadership.
Billy J. Brooks, that was that was Fred
Hampton's right-hand man. So you you
guys are you sound stupid, you know, to
be honest. You sound like you don't
really know what you're talking about.
Doing a lot of hooting and hollering and
don't really know what you're talking
about. If you watch Huey Newton, Huey
Newton's speech, he specifically says,
"We are not black nationalists. We are
internationalists and we stand with all
oppressed people across the globe. No
matter what your ethnicity is,
>> all power to all people."
>> And that's what it's going to take.
Let's get back on track. Well, we were
we was already on track. This is I'm
hoping people see though. And this uh
chairman Paul Bird song. You can follow
him on the Instagrams. You know, there's
there's folks who I really think have
thought that the Black Panthers kind of
like receded into
I don't know just some little like club.
>> And no, the Panthers are still going.
And of course, they were suppressed.
However, the call is out for there to be
a return. And if you're looking for
somewhere to find community and to find
purpose, find out if there's a Black
Panther Party uh chapter in your town.
Mark Wayne is a whole white man and he
had that Panther beret on y'all. And he
was like, "That's where I found my home
with the Panthers." So,
>> weren't there like white Panthers?
Weren't there like
>> white Panthers? Which to me doesn't have
the same ring to it. It feels very
Like it feels very Sigman and uh Roy
like Vegas like
>> can can I start the tigers? The yellow
tigers.
>> There is but I think there is the yellow
pan. I think there is one.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Well, okay. Like but
tigers is like our
Yeah. Our Korean animals.
>> Um maybe I'll start the tigers.
>> I'll bring the tigers. Yeah,
>> bring the Tigers because
>> start that chapter.
>> The White Panthers just feels like the
name of like a Liz Taylor,
>> like a Teeu version of the Black
Panthers.
>> It just feels like a scent. Yeah.
>> White Panther. White Panther.
>> Oh my god.
>> You know what it is? White Panther would
be the scent for cougars. Like that's
what they would market to cougars. Yes,
>> cougars wear white panther.
Big cat energy.
Oh my gosh. Um, the answer to the
question, who was the man in the video?
That is chairman Paul Birdong. I
actually don't know what chapter he's
the chairman of though. I haven't been
able to get there. But you know, you
follow him,
>> Laura?
>> I do. Yeah, I do. you.
>> Mhm.
>> That was the same guy from the first
video. Is it?
>> Yeah. No. Yes.
>> You know what? I didn't give him all
that hype. That's the same. So, it's
it's Philly. It's Philly.
>> Yes. I started following him because I
was like, who is this man?
Who
is this? Wow.
>> Okay.
>> Yes.
>> All right. Paul Bird song. You know I'm
gonna get him on the show, right?
>> I was going to say if please get him on
the show.
>> I will be reaching out to him.
>> Yes. Um
>> so where do we leave off? We were on
Uranus and Gemini and this is the Uranus
return for the United States and Israel.
uh because Israel was founded on May
14th, 1948. And so look out for a change
of what's going to happen in Israel. And
then this is also the Uranus return for
Joseph Robert Biden Jr., Donald J.
Trump, South Korea, Bernie Sanders, and
the partition between India and Pakistan
via the British. So all of these things
that I just
>> said have Uranus and Gemini.
>> So something is going to change with
these people and these places and Uranus
is like breaking apart. Um so I think
the the Uranus return of the United
States is going to possibly break up the
Union, break up the United States. I I
think I said that last year. Um, and for
for Israel, they're trying to expand
their borders, right?
>> I think that's what's happening. I think
Zionists are trying to break up the
United States that they can usurp it
under the the flag of Israel. Like they
literally, when they're talking about
like Donald Trump will be a third-term
president, it's because I think that in
their minds, they are going to literally
dismantle the United States and instate
a new country that he would be the
president of. Mhm.
>> Like that's what they have in their
minds.
>> And they literally called him like the
first Jewish president.
>> Oh god.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. And it's it's his Uranus return
too. So
um and then so that's Uranus and Gemini.
>> So I just want to say something here
based on the research that I've been
doing. It's not that the it's not that
the United States is trying to become
the center of the world because I think
what folks are failing to understand is
that none of the decisions that have
ever been made have been made
independently as Americans. They were
made and funded by folks from Europe.
And because we don't have that context,
we are not seeing how um Oh, my bad.
Adrienne was talking about Israel. Carry
on.
I should have known that I was wrong.
Yes, she meant wrong. So, yes. Gone.
>> How dare you?
>> Someone said need to run to office. Do
you see what's happening? There's not
going to be no office TO RUN FOR, Y'ALL.
OH MY GOD. YOU BETTER RUN FOR YOUR LIFE.
>> YEAH. Somebody said that there's not
going to be an election. And I really
think that's true.
>> There's not.
>> Yeah, there's not going to be an
election.
>> I saw someone say yesterday like, "We
have three more years of this." And I'm
like, "Oh my gosh.
How? It's only been one year.
>> Mhm.
>> How can you think that this is going to
end in three years?
>> Keep talking. I need some chocolate. Um,
can you put up the slides again? Cuz I
can't see where we are.
Okay, she walked away.
Um, so after I said Uranus and Gemini,
let's see, where are we?
Oh, I said Mars and Uranus conjunction
in Gemini
and then
Okay.
Oh, you needed me. Damn it.
>> Yes, I needed you to Thank you. Okay.
And I didn't know if you wanted me to
keep going without you here. Um,
okay. So just to go to the actual
transits of this, this is the chart for
the Venus and Jupiter conjunction on
June uh June 9th, 2026. And as you can
see, the United States also has Jupiter
and Venus in its chart. So how they are
using this ca uh this cancer stellium is
the shadow aspect of cancer is like
homeland and protecting our borders and
nationalism
uh because you because the United States
is using Christian nationalism as its
like uh you know I don't know
>> like its banner.
>> Yes. Thank you. It's banner. It's like
it's it's a way of saying like we have
to protect our home. We have to
>> it's called to arms. That's what it's
like.
>> Thank you.
>> Uh so then that means that the United
States is going through its Jupiter and
Venus return. So I think they're using
it more to you know expand their borders
to recruit people to ICE. Um, ICE was
created in March of 2003,
the same month, same year the US invaded
Idoch. So, it is the imperial boomerang.
So, anytime the United States goes
abroad and does its like imperialism
there, at the same exact time the United
States enacts it on their people, it's
not even like we have to wait like a
month for the boomerang. It's like it
happens at the same time. So that's
what's going on there. But I think
individually you can think about using
this transit uh you know to
to
engage in community and to make
relationship to fortify and invest in
relationships. And again, this is going
to be one of the things I suggest. Um,
and this is one of the transits I would
suggest you start or I mean, you should
be starting already, but maybe you can
do some sort of action or community care
thing on that day.
And then this is what day is this again?
>> June 9th, 2026.
>> Community care. Okay.
>> So, sealing squad.
>> Seal squad. Let's mark that on our cow
June 9th as a day that we will either
get together digitally or physically.
So, let's just put that on the cow.
Amanda Landers and Seal Squatterers. So,
let's like
>> mark it.
>> Wait. I love that. And it could even be
like a healing event, like a sound
healing event or something that's maybe
you don't even have to like talk, but
you're together and you're doing an
activity together. Can we do like a um
what do they call it? Like a silent
disco.
>> I've never been to a silent disco, but I
really feel like I would enjoy it.
>> Oh my god, you would love it. It's
really fun.
And also, everyone has like different
options, so some people are like dancing
to different music. It's really cool. Um
okay, so this is July 4th. So again,
this is the Independence Day,
Independence Day of the United States.
um the Mars Uranus conjunction and as
you can see in the United States natal
chart it has Mars and Uranus in Gemini
natally. So this will be the Mars Uranus
return and returns in astrology is
essentially like when the planet comes
back to the position it was at birth.
>> Okay, so we're almost through. Thank you
all for being here. And why just one
more time, why is the return
such a
imp moment of impetus?
>> Because it signals like a rebirth or
like a new beginning, you know, in
everything in nature, the life cycle,
there's a death and then there's a
rebirth. And so when like if you think
about your birthday, a birthday is a
solar return. That's when the sun goes
back to its position at birth, right?
So, you do and I think it's funny that
people are like, I don't believe in
astrology. Well, you blow out a candle,
right? The fire element of the sun, you
make a wish, you set an intention, and
you like start a new year.
>> Wow. You just really upended a lot of
people's nonsense. You blow with a
candle. It's a fire element. It's a
solar return. Cut it out. So when you
said so when you said that I'm having
like a full moon moment
>> that is because it's a completion
like that I'm having in real life.
A full moon a full moon moment is when
the sun is opposite the moon. And so
there's like the two luminaries in
astrology when they're opposite each
other there's like you see something
very clearly.
>> Something is like
Undeniable.
>> Undeniable. And then so with that
undeniability, you choose something. You
change course. You choose change
direction.
>> I can see clearly now the rain is gone.
I can see all obstacles in my way. Okay.
>> Exactly.
>> It's just like it's it's very like now I
can't unsee.
>> Mhm.
>> There's a path.
Oh my gosh.
No pressure. No press. No press. Um, and
then on August 12th, there's a solar
eclipse in Leo. Um, August 28th, there's
a lunar eclipse in Pisces. I'm just kind
of going through these just so people
can have these dates. Um, but I'm not
necessarily going to go in depth. Um,
August 31 fir 31st I really like because
Jupiter and Leo will trine Saturn and
Aries in two fire signs and Jupiter and
Saturn are the timekeepers of astrology
and they're finally coming to an exact
trine and this is a great day to like
forge something that you're growing for
the long term. Um, and I really like
this day to do something creative. uh
creatively express yourself.
Um okay, so then the last transit of
2026,
I was going to say five. Oh my gosh. Um
is between October 3rd and November
14th, there will be a Venus retrograde
between the signs of Scorpio and Leo.
And all retrogrades are reflection and
sort of doing an audit of all the
Venujian things. So Venus rules things
like our value, our self-confidence, our
relationships. So during the fall, we're
all going to kind of go into that era
where we're like, okay, what are my
values? What and how do I want to invest
my money and my time and are the people
in my life currently aligned to those
things?
>> I'm just taking it off the screen so you
can lean into this a bit more,
>> okay? because I want people to really
hear what you're saying. Okay.
Yeah. Um
and you know, when you listen to some
astrologers, they're going to say, "Oh,
your ex is going to maybe pop up from
the past or or you know, you're going to
go through a breakup." And I think it's
true, but I think the crux of a Venus
retrograde is to check your values. And
like it's so simple to think about like
we don't have we have a in we have a
finite amount of time and money is the
currency that currently we all need
right we live we still live in
capitalism. So how do you want to use
the finite time and money that you have
and who do you want to spend your time
with? And I think this is important
because
again the three suggestions that I'm
going to have
is all sort of like um about this Venus
retrograde too.
So I have um I think the last slide is
um
okay
so I have three remediations for 2026
and remediation in astrology is like how
you address the challenging planetary
placements or transits. It's about
taking conscious action by engaging with
the planet's themes. So, I'm not an
astrologer that's like, "Bury your
>> I'm not like bury your head in the sand
or,
>> oh, I can't wait till this transit
leaves." No.
>> Okay.
>> The the like everything in life, there's
going to be an expansion and a
contraction. There's going to be a death
and life, a rebirth. There's going to be
light and dark. And I'm sorry not to be
that person, but who said that life's
going to be easy? Like listen, Coleplay
said nobody said it was easy. I mean, no
one ever said it would be this hard, but
we'll take it back to the start.
Literally. Literally. So, like when you
go to an a Vadic astrologer or a Chinese
astrologer, this is why I like the
Asians because literally they'll be like
>> this is like the Asians. No, because
literally they'll be like, "This is bad
luck. This is bad luck, but this this is
how I can help you." And so in like
Chinese astrology, that's why they use
like amulets and they funue and like
acupuncture to help remediate some of
these like difficult astrological
things, right? So my three remediations
for 2026, I tried to keep it very
simple, very high level. The first one
is connection. Now connection to self
first and foremost that means doing the
inner healing connecting to the divinity
within you and your ancestors and to
elevate your consciousness. Because what
I see a lot of in activist spaces is
people don't commit to their own
self-growth and healing. So then they
perpetuate these very trauma patterns
that we're trying to break.
>> Yeah. And
>> I can I can attest to that.
>> Like myself.
>> Yes.
>> Like I had to check myself about that.
Like literally I've been feeling I was
just feeling very emotional this morning
and it was like
I
I I feel like I am going to allow myself
to get stuck if I don't challenge myself
to
>> be more active outwardly with the
divinity work that I've been doing
inwardly
>> and like how does that show up? Like it
would have been really easy yesterday
when I heard that like Joel Santana said
he like literally doesn't make sense.
Like it would have been really easy to
do a video about like how dumb that is
cuz that's like obvious, right? But
that not that's not divine.
>> Like you know like even in in what would
the ancestors say and when I was doing
the show as a um one woman show I was
leaning into just like the lowhanging
fruit of like Clarence Thomas is whack.
So we're like making jokes about that
and then I realized like no if this is
going to be a useful tool with art.
>> You have to give a deeper exploration to
how he became whack because the goal is
about redemption, right? The goal is
like how do we redeem ourselves? How do
we course correct? And even if it's not
possible for him, how do you use his
story as like a path for others to see
through?
>> Yes.
>> Does that make sense?
>> Oh my god. 100%. And like we're all such
multifaceted, multi-dimensional people
who have an origin story. We have our
villain era. We have our traumatized
era. And so I think, you know, that's
why I always try to give people a chance
because you never know like at what
point of a person's journey you're like
meeting them at.
>> Yes.
>> And that's why I think like K-pop demon
hunters, it's about Korean shamanism. It
is like each and every one of us has a
demon inside of us and it's not to like
pretend that it's not there but to
transmute that part of us and allow the
whole of us to shine. Like that was like
the crux of that.
>> It's very Carl Young, you know, like
>> very Carl Young.
>> I think there's also just the reality of
thinking that you can shun something and
it's going to go away is not actually
how anything works.
>> No. And that goes for you as a person,
too. Like when I think of like what was
my villain era, I'm like
>> I feel like my villain era was
>> when I was letting my trauma rule me,
>> right? So like I'm I am doing the whole
like I have an opinion and I'm going to
say it even though it's like not even
really thought out. Like it's mean. It's
just you're just being mean. Um but
that's my trauma talking. And so now
like when I get to this point I can
recognize in other people like you think
that's an opinion you're just being mean
>> like
>> and and you know maybe sit with that
like why why does that feel like a thing
that you need to do? Um so I love I love
this and by the way I mean no pressure
but like this right here is a framework
that I could build my whole 2026 off of.
>> Yes.
>> Like this right here. So y'all don't
think I just be having guests on because
like I'm cool with them. No, it's people
that actually like this right here is
cuz like the
it's just such a
Okay, tell me if you agree with me on
this. I feel like the need for like
super clarity and direction has just
become more and more necessity in
>> Oh, 100%.
>> Okay. Like we we were talking through
Instagram DMs that like the power of our
minds and the ability of manifestation.
We just as a collective haven't come
together. If we all sink our minds and
cuz what you focus on expands, right?
And if everything and everywhere is
already created in the quantum realm,
then we can literally all be on the same
synced page and that have the clarity of
vision of what like we want to see. And
it's just that I know people like, you
know, are listening to this if they
don't if they haven't come on this
journey yet. They're like, what the hell
is she talking about? But um but if we
can manifest on the individual level, we
can also manifest in the collective
level. And that's what we've been doing,
but we've only been manifesting the
trauma and the violence and the, you
know, the the the trauma patterns from
our past. That's why I keep calling it
trauma patterns because we haven't known
anything else. And so that's why number
three is creativity. Like we need to use
our imagination and our ability to be so
delusional
that there is a timeline that is
emerging because timelines are working
all at the same time but we can't see it
yet. We're all focusing our attention on
the death of this thing. We're all
focusing on like the ice raids and and
the bombing and but that is the death.
That's the physical manifestation of a
death of empire. But there's something
else emerging that we also have to focus
our attention on and start creating the
structure Saturn the structure to let it
emer
this is the epiphany I had this morning
literally like so I'm like ah I'm like
holding on to my bun because this was
the epiphany I had this morning I
realized that like
>> I was in that space of just like
>> the the reporting on and that responding
to the the things of the now. And it's
not to say that there isn't any efficacy
or necessity for that. But I Amanda,
that's not my space. Like I'm I'm
actually I feel like far more useful in
the imagining and the building of
something else because as an artist
>> Yes. the ushering like as an artist, as
a leader, as a visionary like that's
where my real
>> capabilities and gifts like I'm smart.
So I can do this other thing, but my
gifts like my supernatural gifts are in
taking something from nothing. Making
something from nothing.
>> Yes.
>> And actualizing. Like someone said to me
the other day like, "You are the most
actualizing mofo I've ever met." Because
I'll be like, "Oh, I want to do it." And
now it's done. Y'all said you wanted an
Amanda Summit
>> and you got an Amanda Summit. But that I
I I just feel so full hearing you say
that because I think a lot of people
need to hear that to also give them
permission
to not be
fully consumed by the old by all of the
now
>> because there's I think a there's a
guilt that I think some people feel have
about like okay but can I look forward
>> and it's like yes that's also a part of
understanding the now.
>> Yes. But that's why it's it's important
for people to grieve. You have to grieve
what was and continue to do that
transmuting process. That's why this is
deeply spiritual work because you can't
move forward if you haven't grieved the
past. So for those of us who have done
that work for the last two years, it's
our responsibility to hold the vision
for the future that people don't see
yet. Like there's the prophetic people
that can already see that. And I feel
like I'm one of those people. Like I'm
already living in a timeline that's like
not
>> She says this all the time.
>> I say this all the time. I'm like Amanda
my my consciousness is like 10 years
from now and it looks great. We just
have to and then I come back to this
timeline. I'm like okay people like this
is what we got to do you know and so
there we need people we need
>> behaviors
>> literally. Oh my god I love that. We
need those people who are the death
doulas of empire. Like we need the
people who are in this moment, right? We
need those people. Everybody has a role.
>> And then we need the people who are
ushering in and focusing our attention.
That's why we need to share our ideas.
Yes.
>> Like what do you see? What does it feel
like? This is all a part of like
manifestation, but we have to
collectively do it. Now
>> I'm definitely having a gathering in my
house. Um,
number two, which is like something that
I always hesitate in talking about is
community because being in community is
not easy. By the way, um,
>> everybody trying to figure out how to
text somebody for for like four days now
>> who's in my community. I've been trying
to figure out what to text them for 4
days.
>> Yes, everyone says it online, but then
when when I meet them in person, I'm
like, you're a terrible villager. What
are you talking about? Um,
like you're a terrible villager. Is that
>> what I say? No, I say that. I'm like,
you're terrible person. What the hell?
Uh, com I think community really is a
commitment to self-growth and
self-awareness and having conflict
resolution. 90% of people I meet are
conflict avoidant. And so you cannot be
in a community if you avoid conflicts.
I'm sorry. Like so community and being
in one is probably the most difficult
thing, but we need that to organize, you
know, like we and and maybe you need
different pockets of community. Like I
have tears and I have like different
kind of communities. You have your
community that you like sort of like
ideiate with and dream with and you have
the one that where you do like direct
actions with you know you have ones that
are like your immediate community like
your neighbors who you can call upon. So
these are things that these are three
things everybody can focus on for 2026
because based on the astrology
um
so based on the astrology this is what
we the people can do. Okay. So there's
like this moment in July. Sorry. Did you
want to say something?
>> I just wanted to say something before
you go on to like the culmination of
this. By the way, Olivia, check your DMs
in um Patreon.
Um,
you often say art will save us.
>> What do you mean by that?
>> Okay. So, I think you started to say it
like art gets us to think creatively,
right? It it brings us out of our
current
not not situation but like it allows us
>> the grid.
>> Yes.
And we need that's why artists are so
important. That's why they defund arts
first. They defund music first, right?
Because for us to imagine something
outside of these systems is dangerous.
And so that's why I think art will save
us because
um
like
the antithesis of that is a colonial
mind which is like all of us being the
same thing, all of us being beige, all
of us thinking the same way. Yeah, Crate
and Barrel or what is that other one?
Um,
>> Pottery Barn.
>> Pottery Barn. Thank you.
>> It's a Crate and Barrel Pottery Barn
aesthetic. Like the fact that everything
is white and the diversion is cream,
right? Cream and beige. Like
if you've been to my house, well, you
all have seen my house.
>> It is defiantly
anti Pottery Barn. And in Grenada,
the homes are literally like every color
of my shirt. And it feels even on such a
basic level as like a strike back at
colonialism that they're like, "We're
going to paint these houses every
freaking color possible and there's not
going to be any order to this."
>> Um,
>> you know, Herby Hancock, I met him one
time, and I've talked about this before,
but I'll reiterate it because it really
aligns here. When I met him, I said
something pretentious like, you know,
just everybody isn't an artist. And he
was like, eh, everybody's an artist. And
I was like,
like, what do you mean? And he said,
everybody has the ability to create.
Like that's part of the human design.
And we are creative in many ways.
Sometimes people have to be creative
because they have a lack of. And so
there's necessity breeds innovation.
Sometimes people are creative because
they have an imagination and they want
to see things happen. And sometimes
people are creative because they can see
things working in ways that others
aren't. So he was like, you know,
engineers are creative. Um, visual
artists are creative, pianists are
creative. He's like, creativity and in
the human form has takes on many forms.
And what I when I look at when I listen
to what you're saying and I look at how
all of these things combine, it's like
>> I feel like what I'm seeing is
um Oh my god, where' we go? The last
one,
>> connection, community and creativity
like have to merge
>> like community being connected in a
creative vision of what is possible.
>> Yes. They're all inter like the ven
diagram. They're all interconnected.
>> Connected
>> essentially. Yeah. Like a place where
you could start is like what is your art
practice? cuz like I think when people
hear creativity they think of it so
literally like I'm painting.
>> For the record, Laura is an incredible
artist. I just want to make that clear
because that's not been put out there.
>> Thank you. And it just is. You are you
came here on earth at this specific
moment in history all of us did to
create something and you are just the
physical vessel to channel that which is
your responsibility to find the medium
for you know so like all of us some of
us
>> again
>> so I just got that download
>> okay I don't know if I okay
>> okay I think what you were saying like
tell me if tell me if I'm saying what
you're thing. You were brought here
for whatever reason and your time here
is estab is establishing and
understanding that reason and putting it
into reality,
putting it into action.
>> Yes. So you came here as a spiritual
creative being because we are all
creators on this specific time in
history to be the vessel for
that thing
>> to that you're creating but it's your
responsibility to find the right medium.
So, for some people it's music. For some
people it's podcasting or art, literally
film. Um, it's creating children
literally or like whatever it is like
you your responsibility is to figure out
what your thing is.
>> Can we get the woo box real quick?
>> Yes. The woo box.
>> The Gia theory
>> is that I think I've texted this to you
before. Y'all need to know that Laura is
my woman friend that I can text I can
text Laura anything. it doesn't matter
how woo woo it is and she'll be like
absolutely or she'll be like well I
think and I appreciate you for that and
I'm very happy that I found you
>> thank you
>> um
the Gaia theory is that earth is an
ecosystem that is like self-healing self
everything which by the way is how you
know earth is feminine because like the
vagine is self cleaning for the record
>> um so the the theory which I agree with
is that everything on earth serves a
purpose to continue the growth of earth
to continue the existence of earth to
continue the expansion of life right
that's the goal
>> and so in that context it's like well if
we are here as physical beings that are
in direct correlation with the earth
like we breathe the air that plants let
give give off and plants breathe the air
that we give off, right? So, we're in
direct connection with it. Then we have
like every other aspect of Earth a
purpose in the expansion of Earth and
life on Earth. And so, to your point,
it's like what is that, right? And what
is the human
>> version of that that is enacted and done
differently than necessarily like
leopards or turtles etc. Because every
animal has a purpose in the ecosystem
except for humans at this point in life.
Indigenous people knew that.
>> That's true.
>> Indigenous people knew like, oh, my
purpose here is to do XYZ, you know,
like we're supposed to do this. Every
animal has a purpose in the ecosystem.
Not one of them can you be like, oh,
they they made a mistake with the
mosquito. Like, they all serve a
purpose.
>> What is ours
>> is an individual journey as well as as a
collective journey. I mean, I think what
we're seeing right now is a lot more
awakening to the collective awareness
that we've had a lack of awareness about
that and that colonialism is what
created it.
>> Yes, I 100% agree with that. Yeah.
>> All right. Well, we solved it. So,
>> we did it. We did it.
>> So, you know, go forth, guys.
Um because every time I think for a
second, even just for a moment, every
time I even if I just think for a moment
like maybe we're just here to die. Like
maybe we're just here like maybe there's
no real purpose to this. Like we're just
here as best as as beings and we die.
Then I see something or hear someone say
something that's like nope. Because I
sent Laura a video last night where this
scientist is essentially like
we are all like we're made of cells and
every single cell in our body has the
same knowledge as the other cells. So he
was like that's you can't refute that as
a like very
um
important aspect to understanding like
our our like role as something greater.
And
>> I'm not going to play the video yet
because I know you had things to say but
I just wanted to
>> Oh no it's okay. Well, no. That's why I
think to be a colonizer
if if we're talking about aliens. Okay.
I think
>> I think
>> you just made you just made a bunch of
people in the chat very happy. Like
finally we getting to the aliens.
>> They're already here. First of all,
second of all, I think there's different
types of aliens. And I think because
we're all interconnected literally
through ourselves and we have mirror
neurons to be able to colonize and and
rape and pillage somebody like people
you have to be so disconnected to your
soul and your body. So I think like if
we're tracing back the origins of
colonization I think that first one was
an alien like not of this earth
basically.
Listen, so one time me and comedian Sam
Jay, we were having brunch at the Moon
Tower Comedy Festival in Austin, Texas.
By the way, guys, I was a whole stand-up
comic for 13 years.
Hilarious.
So, we were at brunch and she was like,
"These white people are aliens, man.
And I was like, "Expound?" And she was
like,
>> "Yeah, because
I mean, how is it that they the only
ones that the son be messing up and just
be messing them up?" And she went on
this whole rant about it and then she
ended up putting it in a special that
she did on HBO, but I've never forgotten
it because it started as her just having
us a conversation with me like,
>> "I don't know, man. It's not adding up.
Like how do people just don't care? Like
that it's just it don't make sense.
>> I feel like
>> to your point when I see behaviors in
certain folks, I'm just like
>> that doesn't feel human. Like I don't
feel like that feels like you are the
descendant of something other than and
that it's like because it just and maybe
and maybe Laura
>> maybe we're just saying this because we
don't want to believe that humans can be
bad but
>> I also like to believe
that there's really no limitations to
what you what you can believe.
>> Yeah. But also I I Okay. Yeah. I do
believe in the alien thing too, but also
um I do believe in dark energies and I
and people like Elon Musk and Mark
Zuckerberg, like Peter Teal, Donald J.
Trump, like I do think some
>> I do think you you give up your soul in
exchange for power. And I do think
there's something to that, too. Well,
they're all part of like
cults,
>> you know, and organizations that are
ancient and that have practiced
>> cult.
>> We know we So, let me just say something
that's not woowoo. People are going to
think it's woowoo, but it's not.
>> The earth is power.
>> Yes,
>> the earth is magnetized. Like the earth
is an actual functioning.
>> It is emitting power all the time. So
the idea that there are people who have
been able to harness that power is
honestly the the idea that people look
at that as like some crazy notion is
stupid to me. There's power in plants
witches do the power of plants. Like
there's electromagnetic power literally
they've done a study that like tribal
elders
and I think it was the Lakota tribe. I'm
all was like I think it was the Lakota
tribe like
>> they did a test between like uh rain
dances and um like seeding the clouds
and the rain dances were more effective
at creating the rain because when they
actually like got to the bare bones of
the electromagnetic the people had fig
like traditions had cultivated over time
an ability to understand what
um rotations and formations that they
need to be dancing in to whip up the
electromagnetic
power of the earth.
>> Mhm.
>> Right. So like none of this is
subjective you guys. Like this isn't
like a oh Amanda she's out of here. Like
no this is just the facts. That's we we
also have seen it like windmills hydro
power all of this is using the power of
the earth.
>> So if we see all of that
>> and then we know that then we know that
there are people who can use that from
ill. Oh, well they were like psychics
that were named in the Epstein files.
Like they use these psychics to do
remote viewing to do some sort of like,
you know, uh, spells and witchcraft. So
yeah, of course. I don't know why we're,
you know, like I don't because people
love to like say keep themselves safe
because they don't know that power, but
the power is there. And and I just feel
like the the trick of these folks has
been to convince us that we don't have
access to that power for good.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah.
>> Yes. There's also electricity in our
bodies. Like our bodies are literally
electric. It's electric. Boogie woogie
wgie.
>> I was doing my 20 minutes of movement
because I do 20 minutes of movement
every day now. And this morning I was
doing my 20 minutes of movement and I
was electric sliding by myself. And when
I tell y'all I was having a
The cats and the dog were like they're
all staring at you like
>> Yes.
>> Jordy was literally just sitting on the
couch like you enjoying yourself. I'm
like
>> so you know that's why like the when
people sh like poo poo on astrology I'm
like you're missing the point.
Anything that colonizers have rendered
as nonsense, you should be learning.
>> Mhm. Cuz they're using it on you. So
>> yikes. I love when people are like,
"Don't bring politics into this." I'm
like, "Well, politics is doing you,
honey." Like, I don't know what to tell
you. I don't know what to tell you. All
of it is like someone said, like Rolando
said Bible here. Like there's astrology
in the Bible. Like
>> Yes. Mhm. All over the place.
>> All over the place.
>> Um,
>> that star that the three magi followed,
what do you think that is?
>> Just so correct me if I'm wrong, anybody
in the comments, this is going to be a
quick dubtail. After the magi gave the
gifts, did they just bounce? Because I'm
just wondering how you show up with
gifts to a manger and none of those
gifts can actually help you like get a
better crib, right? Cuz like
cuz like maybe gold but like who knows
if they even use gold in that part of
the world and like
so like after you see me in this manger
you bounced. You didn't say like yo
y'all let me let me see cuz cuz we're
also like the magi they're nomadic but
like that means they got a whole squad.
I just find that very that part of the
story is just
and then I read something the other day,
Laura Chung,
that said the story of Jesus and all of
that
was in eight other religions prior to
Christianity. The whole setup, the whole
birth, the whole situation
>> was the ground was the cornerstone of
eight religions prior to the birth of
Christianity. So it was just like
>> Oh, like the same exact story with the
same people.
>> Yeah.
>> Interesting.
>> Yeah. So I'm just like that part of the
story as a kid was always like, "So hold
up.
Away in a manger,
>> no room for a bed.
>> The little Lord Jesus laid down his
sweethead.
>> Yeah. Well, they were like fleeing. They
were like, "They're going to kill us."
>> But then but but then the magi popped up
and left them there, bro.
>> Yeah. Well, maybe the magi, you know,
how we interpret the magi in astrology
are the magicians. like they're people
who um study astrology and they you know
that's why they followed the star. So I
don't know if they had real power at
that time. I know somebody correct me if
I'm wrong.
>> I just feel like if you rolling up with
gold you could you could you could get
another house another crib in the end. I
don't know. I'm just saying
I'm just saying these are the types of
things as a child I was very disturbed
by. I could never get past that. And
>> yeah like the math was not math thing.
>> No. And that's when I knew like, oh,
this is allegory.
>> This isn't maybe they just envisioned
these three folks popping up because
here
>> I studied the historical
Jesus like outside of the Bible and like
that the three ma the three magi were
actual people, you know, but um yeah,
>> I could see confusing.
>> We never got teenage Jesus.
M
>> we never got teen Jesus. We got Teen
Wolf.
>> We got Teen Witch.
>> We never got Teen JC.
>> Someone write a fanfiction.
>> Write a fanfiction. Make the Apostles
have matching jackets.
>> I'd actually watch that. Like, you know,
I'd actually watch that. like the Lion's
Den is really like is is more it's like
he gets trapped in like the locker room
of the like opposing team and their
mascot is the Lions.
>> Mhm.
>> And so he has like a really deep
conversation with like the mascot. Like
I can do all of this y'all. I can do
this for days. Like
Daniel's over there. He's like, "Daniel,
what happened?" He's like, "Oh my god,
the Lions."
So, I don't know how we got here and I'm
not even worried about it, but is there
anything else that you would like to
impart to us? The brilliant
>> Laura Ch.
>> Well, does anybody have questions? Um, I
guess, yeah, just like I I went over the
dates of 2026. So, you want to mark
those dates in your calendar. Think
about how you want to use those
energies. again like remediation is to
use the planetary energy in a conscious
way versus just like hiding away and
being like, "Okay, I'm just going to
bury my head in the sand for the rest of
2026."
And those three things I suggested for
you to cultivate. So, connection,
community, creativity,
and um and yeah, that's
>> all right.
Okay. I guess TBD until like 2026
actually starts to unfold.
>> Is there anything about
this um year that you want people to
really see as like that you want people
to really change their relationship to?
Um, like for instance,
I love when you talk about that
it's like it it can be a challenge
versus a hindrance.
>> Can you just like speak to that a bit
more because we're entering challenging
times?
>> Yes.
>> And I really like your perspective on
that.
>> So I I teach astrology, right? So
there's this thing in astrology called
essential dignities where it is based on
a colonial language because you have to
think about when astrology was founded
through ancient times there was such
thing at that time still of slavery and
colonization. Right? So the language is
very colonial. We talk about rulerships,
planets that rule certain signs and then
planets that are in detriment or exile.
And I always say like I I use this as a
metaphor for like planets that are in
rulership. So let's say Saturn is in at
home in the signs of Capricorn and
Aquarius. I I don't like to use language
of like good or bad or negative or
positive but maybe better resourced. So
planets in their doicile are like white
Americans in America, right? the systems
>> this they are entitled because they the
systems also support their identity
right and then planets in their exile so
that's like Saturn in Leo and Saturn in
Cancer
they're challenging because like
immigrants to the United States they
don't know the language they don't know
the traditional rules and culture but
what makes immigrants so unique is
they're creative. And I just look at my
parents as like immigrants to this
country. They came here without knowing
the language in their early 20s. They
yes, they had to work harder because
they had to work in New York City in
their early 20s, but they are the most
resilient, creative, funny people to me.
And because I ask my parents all the
time, I'm like, "Are you not scared of
like what's going on?" on and they're
kind of like
>> I know it's fascinating.
>> Americans have no idea what we left the
country that we left like you know and
so when I look at them I'm like oh
there's just so just like yeah like just
creative. So I think when there's a
difficult transit you want to look at it
as like the grain of sand against the
pearl. It's like annoying. Maybe it's a
little challenging. you're a little
uncomfortable, but in the end of it,
you're going to be the best version of
yourself at that, you know, the most
conscious maybe. And that's why I say
like don't turn away from feeling
uncomfortable or the challenges because
like you could be one transit away from
becoming the best version of yourself
and then when you're able to sort of
stand up and face your fears, you are
invited on two shows like Amanda, you
know, like I I would never have
made it this far if I just stood in the
sidelines and remained silent, you know?
It's because I was outspoken about
Palestine. It's because I continue to
show up that people trust me enough to
invite me on and it it helps me to do my
own mission here on Earth. So that's my
little pep talk.
So we do have some questions. Um I do
want to say though that we had the
dovetail we went on was because you were
like I believe that the aliens I believe
that the first colonists were aliens and
that
>> Oh yeah.
>> Sorry.
I was like, "How do we get here?"
>> That always happens. I always go on a
side quest. Sorry.
>> Those are the best. Those are the best.
Okay.
Hamid asked, "Since 2026 is so fire sign
heavy, how are the movements going to
impact uh and position air, earth, and
water signs?"
>> Um, how are the movements going to
impact and position? I think position is
a is a typo, but I think he's meaning
like how are they going to impact the
other signs like
>> Oh god. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> So, if you know your rising sign and you
have a fire or air sign, then the
energies of this year are going to be
more conducive for you. They're going to
help you feel more energized. They're
going to help you feel more like, oh, I
have momentum behind my sales. Whereas,
like the last three years, there was a
lot of water in the air. So that was
actually helping the water and earth
signs
>> for
>> rising and and placements. And so water
water and earth are feminine signs. This
was about like coming into oneself to do
the healing work to be more still to do
you know grief work and to um you know
be more in the feminine energy. And now
this is the these are the years for the
fire signs to go out there and take
action. So if you're an earth and water
sign, the next like three years are
going to be more, you know, um
>> I think all of us are going to have to
take action. But maybe for you it's like
different, right? So it's not so um
outwardly but maybe it's more like
internal you know working with some of
your fears around speaking up perhaps
>> um challenging some of your limiting
beliefs or calcified belief systems.
>> So everyone has to do that work but
>> yeah I've been dancing with the idea of
teaching what I would call a course on
confrontation.
Um,
>> and it would be like a course that
addresses confrontation like in
historical and current instances like
within geopolitical like challenging
as well as
looking at that with ourselves and like
>> asking folks to then do self-exloration
about what they have been avoidant
around.
>> Oo, that's such a good one. Yes.
>> And then the third part would be
um roleplaying.
>> Yes, that's very important.
>> So, this is something I've been like
toying with and I see people in the chat
like, "Yes, please." Um, yes, sir. More
food, sir. Um, please, sir.
Um because I I do you said something
earlier and you said it just now that
confrontation
is definitely contextualized as
negative. We know why because they want
a passive populace. Um
>> however, it's also at the the reality
though is that we have been trained not
to be that.
>> Oh, we've been trained to be obedient to
the system since we were kids.
>> I mean, this is why I've been getting in
trouble all my life. I never get in
enough trouble to get like I've only
been disobedient, but I've never been
like a ruffian.
>> But but teachers either love me or were
like,
>> "Who is this broad?" And I was like,
"I'm seven.
>> I'm seven. Relax."
Okay. X-ray Dove asks, "Do you have a
response when people claim quote unquote
new age practices like astrology and
yoga are of the devil?" I have family
members thinking I'm a dog.
because I'm
>> I'm sorry. I'm I'm not laughing at you.
>> We're laughing with you.
>> It's so funny that that is the response
because all of our indigenous practices
have cosmologies.
Like I I happen to practice the western
tropical system, but like I guarantee
you your ancestors had their own way of
looking at the stars and a system that
was demonized because again they
demonize it because it breaks our
connection to the natural cycles.
>> Yep. You know, so like for me, astrology
was really to help me break break free
of the system of capitalism and how they
impose their timelines and all of this
stuff onto you and you're just like,
wait a minute,
why why is it late? Like as a 40
something woman, like why is why are
they telling me that I'm a geriatric
person? It's like
>> right
>> when when in astrology after the age of
like 44 you're actually rising in your
life you know like so yeah
>> wait really
>> yes they're called per annual perfection
years so 44 45 46 47 48 they're like
you're you're at the top of your chart.
So yeah, but then but then you have like
these people being like, "Oh, you're too
old." And you know, and you're just
like, "Shut up." No, I'm not.
>> That's what I'm saying. That's what I'm
saying. Like they're like, "You're not
that girl." AND I'M LIKE, "I I I'm more
that girl now than I ever was."
>> Literally,
that's why you see like 40 mid-40 women
like now they're divorcing their
husbands. Now they're having their like
crash outs because you're told since
you're young to center men, center
marriage,
serve your family, do all these things.
And it's like, wait, who who said like,
>> who?
>> I have a home girl who does like a
podcast with other women and they did an
episode about divorce because one of the
women on the podcast is getting a
divorce and they had a divorce lawyer.
No, they had a notary on a not a a
notary on and she was like, "I cannot
stress to you all how my business is
booming."
>> Mhm.
>> Because so many women are getting
divorced.
>> Yeah.
>> She was like, "That's literally why my
business is booming is because I keep
getting called to come and do notary
services for divorce papers and for f
like for filings and whatnot." And it's
something the the percentage is nuts.
It's like it was 30% 5 years ago and now
it's 60%. Like it's something bonkers
and it's all women.
>> Yeah, I 100% believe it just from my own
like friends and family.
Um,
did I answer that question by the way?
The person that asked that question?
You did, but I mean I feel like you can
give like a specific quippy like well
>> um which you are capable of doing.
>> Well, I did say that they demonize these
practices to cut us off from our own
like practices that connect us back to
ourselves and nature.
I think there's also just something to
be said about
like if they really want to have a
conversation like what do you think
you're doing when you're praying? You're
meditating. Praying is meditating.
>> And at the end of the day, if you you
have a Jesus that you a lot of people
are religious, but they don't it was
handed to them,
>> so they don't know necessarily like
where it came from. So they're studying
someone else's belief system versus
ver versus cultivating their own. But I
think the answer to them is mind your
business.
>> Yeah.
>> I think that's really the mind your
business. And when they say new age,
your very basic response can be
everything I'm doing is older than
everything you're going to study on
Sunday.
>> Literally,
>> that's your quick and dirty.
>> Literally. Um, Rolando, who is one of
our moderators and gets the trolls out.
Go away.
>> Rolando.
>> Roland that. Yes. How did you know he
was one of the girls?
>> Oh, I didn't. I just I just like when I
I just want to say it like that.
>> You nailed it. Ronzo.
>> Um, Miss Chong, I'm a big fan. Doesn't a
return of Jupiter bring expansion? I
think one of your slides showed
America's coming up.
>> Yes. Yes. Well, we're in it now. Um, the
United States is in its Jupiter return.
And if you're personally, if you have
Jupiter in Cancer or Jupiter in Leo,
then you personally are going through
your Jupiter return. So, um, it happens
in increments of 12. So, if you're 36,
48,
oh my gosh, 60, then you're going
through your Jupiter return.
>> I went through that. It was a time.
>> Yeah, it was a time.
It was a time. Okay, now some people are
getting very pacific and I need y'all to
stop doing this. Like, pay for the
reading. Okay, pay for the reading. This
is
>> or join my class.
>> Or join her class. Like, this is her
skill. But for the sake of um promotion,
this question. Morning, Miss Chung.
Double Taurus, living on my Chiron line
for years. Feeling like moving through
mud and depleted, but need to get out of
LA and the US. Any ideas on how to
connect to needed Aries energy?
>> First of all, what's the Chiron line?
So she is referring Oh she sorry I
assumed that
>> well I found Denise but
>> they are referring to astrocarttography
which you can actually find an
astroctographer to find the best like
line for you um to live on
>> like longitude latitude you mean?
>> Mhm. like you basically put your birth
information into the map of the world
and so you could see like um you know
but it really is like based on the
planet and your intention of that place
cuz if you want to let's say um have
more discipline you would move to a
Saturn line if you want to you know
something like this um so I would find
an astro ctographer that aligns with you
and ask them, you know, what is the best
place for me based on like your
intention, like what you want out of a
place and um and yeah, I think that's
the best way you can go.
I would be so curious
to see
where mine lined up and line up because
I've moved at very specific times in my
life
>> and they have been very
fortuitous.
>> Oh, word.
>> That was the word. Yeah, the word didn't
say. But my mom has also moved
and she always says, "Man's like
everything had to line up a particular
way for you to get here."
And it's not like she was in one place.
It's like she literally had to like go
through a series of places to like end
up in the place where my dad was for me
to be born. So it's not like everything
it's not like anything even came to her.
It's like she had to go through a path.
So I would be so curious to chart her
astrological
>> astroctography
>> her
>> astroctography because it's very like
>> yes I also find cuz like all there's lay
lines all over the world and I often
find that places call to me you know so
like I felt very called since 2024 to go
to Korea again because I went in October
2024.
>> Yes. And I tried going last year, but it
just didn't work out. But I just like I
was like, I have to go. I have to go.
And it was like the place was like
pulling me. So I would also suggest like
feeling into your intuition in your body
of the places that are calling to you
too. Uh because I do think that
>> that specific place and the energy of
that place is part of the growth in the
moment.
Um, do you know any astroctographers?
>> My teacher Sam Reynolds, um, who is like
an iconic astrologer, Sam Reynolds.
>> Okay, I'm going to look up Sam Reynolds
because I'm Mui Curioso.
>> You curios
>> and people are mu mui curioso about
where they can sign up for the class.
So, let me make a banner to put on the
bottom of the um page. Where can they
sign up?
um through my website laurk chung.com
and it's under the tab star school and
we start next Wednesday Mercury's day uh
is Wednesdays and that's why I was like
oh did you do this on purpose your your
podcast on Wednesdays
no but
I
find that when I've I well you know this
because you've told me this but like I
literally like sat with what feels like
the right day. And then I remember
asking folks and people were like,
"Wednesday feels like the right day.
Wednesday feels like the right day." And
I was like, "Okay." Because I was, my
natural capitalist mind is Monday.
>> But that's the moon's day.
>> And now I try to not do anything on
Monday. Mhm.
>> Now, I'm trying to treat Monday as like,
well, I'm trying to treat my whole life
as a retiree, but that's another
conversation
because I honestly like thought about it
the other day and I was like, I've been
working since I was eight.
>> I've been paying taxes since I was
eight. I've been hustling like literally
like my entire
entity has been moving in the context of
how do I advance these gifts? Mhm.
>> And I'm just I don't want to think like
that. I don't want to exist like that
anymore.
>> Mhm. Wow. Child star.
>> Yeah.
>> Wow.
>> Child star. And like not just like child
star like cuz even if I wasn't child
star like Doogie Hower, it was still
like I missed out on certain stuff
because I was doing that,
>> right?
>> Like I got pulled out of like our fifth
grade trip to Wakao River Park because
my mom pulled up and was like, "You have
to go audition for Cop and Half." And I
cried the whole way there.
>> And then I did the audition and she was
like, "How was it?" I was like, "Who
cares?" I mean, I booked it.
>> I was gonna say, "Did you sabotage?"
>> No. I mean, I always book the stuff, but
>> like uh I was like I was in gymnastics
and the coach said I got to work out
with I was going to get to work out with
the older girls that day
>> and it was like a huge big deal. And my
mom was like, "Yeah, no. We're going to
audition for a show at Nickelodeon."
>> Oh my god. And you and you got that
right.
>> My brother and me. But you have to walk
like really far from the parking lot to
the audition like place.
>> Cried the whole way.
>> Whole way there. And my mom WAS LIKE,
"OH MY GOD."
>> And then I got it together and went in,
read, and then I I booked it.
>> So I just
>> You're just like naturally talented.
>> It's not even that. It's literally like
a trade. Like acting for me is like like
like something I learned at Devry, you
know what I mean? It's just like a skill
that I just have. I can
>> Yeah. Like I can just like if all else
fails like anybody an actor because I
that I can do.
>> Yeah.
>> So, but I it's just I don't want to
I don't want to hustle anymore. So,
Mondays are moon days.
>> They're moon days.
>> It doesn't mean I'm not working. It
doesn't mean I'm not using my gifts. It
just means I'm changing my relationship
to them.
>> That's good.
>> And um you guys, Laura K. Chung's
astrology class is incredible. I took it
and I feel like one of the notes that I
want to give all of you is it's not
something you can do passively. Don't go
and take the class and think that you're
just showing up to just like lolly gag
or gallivant as a Caribbean parent would
say. Go there
with the spirit of learning and with the
spirit of a student. Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> And I think that I wish I not I think I
wish I had approached it that way from
day one. Like I was present but I didn't
have my mind in like student mode.
>> Yeah. Like I need to take this like
seriously and study and Yeah.
>> Like I take in information differently
when I'm there as a student versus there
as a listener.
>> Does that make sense?
>> Yeah. So, I feel like I was listening as
like as like a
like someone lecturing, but I needed to
be there as
um a a flipping student. So, you know,
you guys don't play yourselves is my
point. And for the record, Laura K.
Chung will tell you we did that in the
last class. So,
you weren't here for that.
>> And I'm going to push you cuz I'm I'm an
Aries. So, I'm going to be like, you
know, this
>> did you study?
>> Um, you taught the last class. That was
your first time teaching that class in
this particular way, right?
>> Yes. The first one.
>> What do you feel like you're bringing
into this one that you learned from the
last one?
>> So, I added three extra like study hall
sessions, one per month, so that people
could have a moment to catch up and ask
questions. And then I also have a TA
now. I have somebody who's going to help
me. She's going to make worksheets. And
>> what?
>> Yeah. So I so I took the suggestions of
the first class very seriously because I
do want again my intention for teaching
is that people are armed with the tools
to not only understand the theory but
take that theory and actually like be
able to read charts on their own.
Because I personally am not of the per
like mind that you should just be
listening to everyone's opinions. What's
your opinion?
>> Like how do you see this transit? You
know, like you have to take
responsibility for your life. And so I'm
like the best way to do that is to teach
people how to fish versus like I'm just
going to tell you the astrology of 2026
and this is how you should use it. No,
like what what how are you going to use
it?
I mean, I had a therapist one time tell
me, you know, your job is to have your
feelings and my job is to interpret them
for you and you're just sitting back and
enjoying the ride. And I was like,
absolutely not.
Last time I'm seeing you. Um, but I
thought you'd really appreciate this.
Uh, Kzie K247 says, "For some people,
astrology seems like a luxury in times
when people are trying to survive, but
today showed me astrology can be a tool
for survival or maintenance, maybe
renewal, amongst other things." Heart.
>> Wow.
I'm honored.
I'm honored. I feel like this was just a
great way to to come back into the fold
of Views for Amanda in this new
colonizer year of 2026. So, thank you so
much for joining us
>> and thank you.
>> I've been saying happy colonizer new
year to people and watching people do
the math and science in their head and
then
>> they're like
>> and then they're like, "Oh, yeah, you're
right." Yeah. And then some people are
like,
>> "Why?" And I'm like, I've got the answer
prepared for you. It will be a Monday.
>> Um, so you guys, you know what to do. Go
to laurk chung.com, go to the star
school tab, and you can also get
readings from Laura K. Chung. So,
there's like three different types of
readings. So, make sure you read what
each reading type is so that you will
get the one that you want. Okay?
>> And again, thank you, Laura, for being
so fast.
>> Thank you so much. Thank you to your
time and knowledge. Everyone is so When
I see Amanda Landers out in the wild,
everyone is so lovely. Thank you.
>> Yay, you guys. You're representing us.
Wow.
My
love hearing that you guys are out in
the wild and and behaving yourselves
and representing
I'm in love.
I'm in La
I'm
laian.